说真的  这只是偶然
It was just dumb luck, honestly.
我在市政大楼后的垃圾箱里发现了无线电零件
I found the radio parts in a dumpster behind the municipal building.
从安全角度来说  这些东西绝不会被丢在那里
They'd never be left there for security reasons,
所以某人肯定把它当成了垃圾
so someone clearly thought it was trash.
但它不是垃圾
But it wasn't trash.
它只是需要一点呵护
It just needed some love.
我印象最深的是一家冰淇淋店
I have the most vivid memory of an ice-cream shop
那里拥有最美味的黑树莓冰淇淋
with the most marvelous batch of black raspberry ice cream.
内幕冰淇淋店
The Inside Scoop.
我经常去那里
I used to go there all the time.
我们说不定在同一天去过
Hell, we might've been there on the same day.
既然如此  你就必须回答一个重要问题
Well, knowin' this, there's a critical question needs answerin'.
什么问题
What's that?
你喜欢蛋筒还是华夫
Cake cone or waffle?
我们就是这样开始聊天的
That's how we started talking,
我们什么都聊
and we talked about everything.
谈天说地  漫无边际
Everything and nothing.
我忍不住相信
I just can't help but believe
这是上天注定让我们见面
that this is a celestially ordained meet-and-greet.
我也没有泄露过
No bean-spillage here, either.
但尤金  我的同伴超级谨慎
But, Eugene, my people are uber cautious.
如果我们离得很近...
And if we're close...
我从没想过离开这地方
I never thought about leaving this place before.
其实我想过
Well, I-I did,
但我从不相信这有可能
but I never let myself believe it was possible.
史蒂芬妮  事实是我非常想见你
Truth is, Stephanie, I'd just very much like to meet you.
但后来我哥哥介入了
But then my brother got involved,
他很不高兴
and he was not happy.
该死
God damn it.
-这不是你想的那样  -是吗
- It's not what you think. - Oh, yeah?
你知道我今天做了什么吗
Wanna know what I did today?
我调查了一起严重通信违规事件
I investigated a massive communications breach.
显然某人在用未授权的电台
Apparently, someone on an unauthorized radio station
与墙外的非正规社区通话
has been talking to a rogue community outside of our walls.
霍恩斯比在严查这件事
Well, then. Hornsby's all over it.
告诉我  这不是你干的
Tell me it wasn't you.
求你告诉我  你不会偷偷跑出去
Please tell me that you were not about to sneak out
去火车场见一个陌生人
to meet some stranger at a rail yard.
我能怎么说呢
What could I say?
麦克斯  这很危险
Max, it's dangerous.
对联邦的所有人来说
For everyone at the Commonwealth,
特别是对我和你来说
but especially for me and you.
我必须走了
I gotta go.
你最好祈祷霍恩斯比没认出你的声音
You better pray Hornsby doesn't realize that was your voice.
我知道我越线了
I knew I'd crossed a line.
有霍恩斯比盯着
And with Hornsby on the prowl,
出去见你是不可能了
getting out to see you was impossible.
然后你和另一个自称是史蒂芬妮的女人出现了
And then you turn up with some other girl calling herself Stephanie.
-她冒用着我的话  -多撒点彩糖
- Using my words... - Extra sprinkles, please.
我的声音
my voice.
打扰了
Excuse me.
那不会是坚果巧克力口味吧
That wouldn't happen to be Rocky Road there, would it?
你看起来很幸福
You seemed so happy...
于是我没有声张
So, I kept my head down.
我不知道还能怎么做
I didn't know what else to do.
谢谢  麦克斯
Thank you, Max. Mm.
你还需要什么吗
Can I get you anything else?
冰淇淋  茶
Ice cream? Tea?
能让我那混蛋儿子消停一天吗
A day without my son acting like a little asshole?
那我给你拿冰淇淋吧
I'll get you that ice cream.
麦克斯
Oh, and, Max?
让银行取消塞巴斯蒂安的信用额度
Have the bank cut off Sebastian's line of credit.
也许这能让他安分点
Maybe that'll whip him into shape.
我有个消息
I've got news.
然后霍恩斯比来见了帕梅拉
Then Hornsby came to see Pamela...
通信里那个人  他终于承认了...
That guy from the comms breach? Finally admitted...
他嚷嚷着你和亚历山大的事
...and he was buzzing about you and Alexandria.
-我一直没有...  -他在谋划什么
- I never - What's he planning?
我不知道
I don't know.
他野心勃勃
He's ambitious.
可能是任何事
Could mean anything.
也可能没事  只是重建
Could mean nothing -- just the rebuild.
穿橙盔甲的讨厌我的那个人
The big guy in the orange armor who hates me.
他是你哥哥吗
That's your brother?
是的  但是  尤金
Yes, but, Eugene --
而你
And you...
你是史蒂芬妮
You're Stephanie?
不  我是麦克斯
No. I'm Max.
没有什么史蒂芬妮
There is no Stephanie.
那其实是我妈妈的名字
Well, it was my mother's name, really --
-对不起  -所以
- I-I-I'm sorry. - So --
对不起
I'm sorry.
行尸走肉
第十一季  第十二集
这里离家很远  兰斯
This is a long way from home, Lance.
是的
It is.
但这些社区非常适合我们的设想
But these communities are perfect for what we're envisioning.
是你的设想
What you'reenvisioning.
我不认为我们需要这样动用资源
I'm not convinced we need to stretch our resources like this.
不顾实力地扩张帝国
Grow your empire further than your power can extend
只会失去帝国
and lose your empire.
我觉得没那么戏剧化
I don't think it's quite that dramatic.
我告诉你什么叫戏剧化
Well, how's this for dramatic?
如果这次不顺利  我们就退出
If this doesn't go well, we're out.
这些人要么自愿永久加入我们
These people are free to stay with us permanently
要么回去自己修家园
or they can go home and finish their own repairs.
家里要做的事已经够多了
There's enough to do at home
我们无暇去操心另一个州的几个小社区
without having to worry about a couple of small communities in another state.
给个机会吧  帕梅拉
Give it a chance, Pamela.
我真认为你会惊喜的
I really think you might be surprised.
快搞好
Let's wrap it up, okay?
他们来了
They're coming.
别动了
Hey. Leave it out.
遮住窗户
Hey, cover that window.
你好
Hello there.
欢迎
Welcome.
亚伦  我是帕梅拉·弥尔顿
Aaron. Pamela Milton.
幸会
A pleasure.
想参观一下吗
Uh, care for the grand tour?
-正合我意  -好
- I would expect nothing less. - Okay.
亚历山大是个自给自足的生态社区
Uh, Alexandria was a self-sustaining ecological community.
我们有饮用水  太阳能板  农作物种植系统
We have water, solar panels, and, uh, a crop system.
这是谁设计的
Who is the engineer?
-我不记得有这个人  - 其实没这个人
- I don't recall anyone from intake. - Uh, no one, actually.
计划是一个联盟社区的领袖给我们的
We got the plans from the leader of an allied community.
玛姬·李
Maggie Rhee.
我们的人研究了设计图  建了出来
Uh, some of our people studied the blueprints, and we built it.
真有趣
Fascinating.
这么偏僻的地方  你怎么保证安全
How do you keep a place like this safe with it being so isolated?
很不容易
Wasn't easy.
打过很多场仗
Fought a lot of fights.
你也是这里的领袖之一吗
You were one of the leaders here?
是的  我猜可以这样说吧
Yeah, yeah, I guess you could say that.
我们都是领袖
We all were.
灾变前你做什么工作
What'd you do before all this?
这不重要
Doesn't matter.
至少对我们来说不重要
Least, not to us, anyway.
她和我记忆中一模一样
She looks just how I remember her.
你认识她吗
What, you knew her?
过去在慈善圈  我们常有交集
Oh, we used to cross paths quite a bit in philanthropy circles back in the day.
但当时我对政治不感兴趣
But I had no interest in politics at the time.
不过她生来善于掌权
She, however, was born to run things.
她是个什么样的领袖
What was she like as a leader?
她接纳了我们
She brought us in.
我们之前从没有遇到过她那样的人
We'd never met anybody like that before.
你钦佩她
You admire her.
对  非常钦佩
Yeah. Very much so.
她为我们建立了这一切
I mean, she built all this for us.
这值得我们为之奋斗
Something worth fighting for.
但这里陷落了
But it fell.
对  但我们总能重建
Yeah, but we always brought it right back.
这里陷落过不止一次吗
It fell more than once?
-是的  -有行尸
- Yeah. - We've got a breach.
留在这里  女士
Stay here, ma'am.
我来
I got it.
见鬼
Shit.
迪安娜是怎么死的
How did you lose Deanna?
她被咬了
She was bitten.
她转变了吗
Did she turn?
我们不得不杀了她  是的
We had to put her down. Yes.
我觉得我在这里看够了
I think I've seen enough here.
早上好  以西结  杰瑞
Morning, Ezekiel. Jerry.
你也早上好  先生
And a good morning to you, too, sir.
好  开始吧
Mm. Okay, let's get into it.
当天早上只能喝水
So nothing but water morning of.
不能吃固体食物
No food. No solids.
我们需要你空腹
We need you on an empty stomach.
什么
Sorry?
医生  我们只是来做例行检查的
Doc, we're just here for a routine check-up.
我被告知这是术前血检
I was told this is pre-op blood work.
确保他病情稳定  能做手术
To make sure he's stable enough for the surgery.
手术
Surgery?
摘除肿瘤
To take out this tumor.
没人告诉过你吗
Did no one tell you?
我以为我还在排队
I thought I was still on the list.
现在你排在最前面了
Well, now you're at the top of that list.
你很走运
You're lucky.
有些人要等好几年
Some people wait years.
费用怎么办
What about his bill?
付清了
He's paid up.
不管是怎么排上的  我都很高兴
Well, however it came to pass, I'm thrilled.
我们会照顾好你的  以西结
We're going to take good care of you, Ezekiel.
好好休息
Rest up.
周五九点见
See you Friday at nine.
太好了
This is so frickin' awesome!
怎么了
Wha-- What is it?
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
拜托  老大  这是好事
Oh, come on, boss, this is good news.
可能是巧合  可能是搞错了
Maybe it's a coincidence. Maybe it's a clerical error.
可能是老天有眼  不管怎样
Maybe it's divine intervention. Either way,
你不觉得你总该转运了吗
don't you think you deserve a little luck?
帕梅拉
Pamela.
瑞秋准备好见你了
Rachel's ready for you.
你们真有福  门口就有这个
You're blessed to have this at your door step.
我们知道
We know.
我听说了海边旅馆的建立过程
I heard how Oceanside came to be.
你们与救世军和低语者的战斗
About your battles with the Saviors and the Whisperers.
这证明了你们社区很有实力
Says a lot about strength of your community.
我很高兴你们能成为联邦的合作伙伴
I'm excited to have you as partners of the Commonwealth.
亚伦说你们想在协议里加上贸易条款
Aaron mentioned there was a trade provision that you'd like worked into our agreement.
有什么问题吗
Something wrong?
我们和山顶寨的领袖玛姬·李谈过
We spoke to Maggie Rhee. The leader of Hilltop.
她说她没有和你们合作
She told us she's not partnered with you all.
我们向山顶寨提出了
We offered Hilltop the same agreement
与亚历山大一样的协议  但玛姬拒绝了
as with Alexandria, but Maggie declined.
亚历山大有过自己的做法
Alexandria's gone its own way before.
但山顶寨和玛姬一直支持着我们
But Hilltop and Maggie have always been there for us.
我们续签了互相保卫条约  我要遵守它
We renewed our mutual protection pact, and I'm gonna honor it.
如果玛姬决定与你们合作
If Maggie decides to partner with you,
我们也会合作  出于对她的尊重
we will, too, out of respect for her.
不然的话  海边旅馆将拒绝
Otherwise, Oceanside's a "No."
问一句  如果你不能在搞砸前
Question -- what was the point of bringing you along
告诉我有用的信息
if you can't give me any helpful intel
我还带着你来做什么
in advance of shit blowing up in our faces?
修缮亚历山大的是你们的人
Your people have been fixing up Alexandria.
行尸进来又不是我的错
It's not my fault the walker got in.
瑞秋和山顶寨的事你应该知道的
You should've known about Rachel and Hilltop.
因为我会读心吗
Because I'm a mind-reader?
你觉得帕梅拉会怎么看这次绕道
How do you think this little detour looks to Pamela?
看起来像我们没准备好
It looks like we're not prepared.
看起来像你没准备好
It looks like you're not prepared.
兰斯  你了解帕梅拉  我不了解
Lance, you know Pamela, alright? I don't.
你没料到这种事  不是我的问题
You didn't anticipate this? It's not my problem.
别再假装你比我更在乎亚历山大了
Stop acting like Alexandria means more to you than it does to me.
现在  我们的目标一致
Right now, you and I want the same thing.
也就是说我们在同一条沉船上
Which means you and I are in the same sinking boat.
玛姬会给我们添麻烦吗
Is Maggie gonna make this difficult for us?
太好了
Huh. Fabulous.
你要知道
So you know?
对帕梅拉来说  非黑即白
This is all or nothing for Pamela.
如果玛姬拒绝  海边旅馆退出
So if Maggie says no and Oceanside walks,
亚历山大也会被断供
Alexandria is cut off.
那我们会自己想办法
Then we'll figure it out.
好呀
Sure.
因为在我们介入前  你们好得很呢
'Cause it was going so well before we stepped in.
没事吧
You alright?
放下枪
At ease.
你一定是玛姬
You must be Maggie.
我已经吃过了
I already ate.
谢谢
Thanks.
那我放在这里
I'll just leave it right here.
给
There you go.
很高兴见到你们
It's good to see you guys.
玛姬
Maggie...
你们为什么信任这些人
Why do you trust these people?
谁说我们信任了
Who says we do?
我何时信任过任何人
When do I ever?
有道理
Fair enough.
看到亚历山大被清理了倒是挺好的
It's good to see Alexandria getting cleaned up, though.
至少他们说话算话
Least their word meant something.
对  有五万人住在那里
Yeah, there's like 50,000 people living there.
至少49.9%都看起来是好人
At least 49.9 seem like decent enough folks.
而且这不是永久的
And it's not forever.
你确定不和我们一起走吗
You sure you don't want to come with us?
你不用独自打拼的
You don't have to do this alone.
抱歉打扰
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
前锋部队发现了尸群
The forward unit picked up a swarm.
我们有一些多余的枪支
We have some extra rifles with us.
所以在他们处理尸群时
So while they're handling that,
弥尔顿总管提议我们一起去打猎
Governor Milton proposed that we all go hunting,
如果你愿意的话
if you're up for that?
动静这么大  会把食物都吓跑的
We'll scare all the food away stomping around like this.
我和玛姬一队  你们自己搭伴
I'll go with Maggie, and you boys pair off.
这次我不需要护卫了  将军
Don't need a minder this time, General.
我们没事的
We'll be fine.
事情怎么会变得这么糟
How did things get so bad?
谁又知道呢
How do they ever?
我见过很多社区
I've met so many communities,
仍然不明白为什么一些社区足够幸运
and I still can't figure out what makes some lucky and
能抵挡住这个世界  而另一些社区不行
able to fight off the world while others can't.
我不相信运气
I don't believe in luck.
有意思
That's interesting.
我感觉你有意见
I'm sensing more of an opinion.
运气就是机遇
I mean, luck is about opportunity.
我不认识比你机遇更多的人了
I don't know anybody who's had more opportunity than you.
既然要实话实说
Well, since we're being honest...
摊开了说  玛姬
Cards on the table, Maggie.
我这次并不想来
I didn't want to come on this tour.
我管理着成千上万人
I have thousands of people under my care
那种责任让我夜不能寐
and that responsibility keeps me up at night.
这就是当领袖的代价
That's the price of leadership.
一切都有代价
Everything costs something.
对我来说  代价是睡眠
For me, it's sleep.
你知道我凌晨三点在想什么吗
You know what I think about at 3:00 A.M.?
我们能信任谁
Who can we trust?
我们如何保障安全
How do we stay safe?
按照我们的标准  你们都是小社区
Your communities are small by our standards.
我不确定与你们往来是否值得
I wasn't sure the risk of going back and forth would be worth it.
那你为什么还来
Then why are you here?
正确的盟友能让我们更强大
The right allies make us stronger.
这个世界属于我们  而不是死人
This world belongs to us, not the dead.
见到你们几位  听到你们的故事
Meeting all of you, hearing all your stories,
证实了我一直坚信的事
has confirmed what I've always believed.
事物有一种自然秩序  如今已经消失了
There is a natural order to things that has vanished,
那种秩序应该被重建
and that order needs to be restored.
这能为我们的孩子提供一个未来
It provides a future for our kids.
1500万个城邦国家为了权力和资源互相争斗
15 million little city-states fighting each other for power and resources
永远不可能提供那种稳定
is never going to be able to provide that kind of stability.
我向你们提供的东西
I'm offering you the same thing
和你们与海边旅馆的互相保卫条约一样
your mutual protection pact with Oceanside did.
一个能保护你们的势力
Someone who has your back.
来了
Yeah.
我只是来看看你
I just thought I'd see how you were doing.
我在做饭
Um, cooking, actually.
你饿吗
...you hungry?
娜比拉和杰瑞给我留了点便餐
Nabila and Jerry left me a buffet.
-好  -比较酥脆
- Okay. - It's, um, crispy.
好
Yeah. Why not?
来吧
Here.
杰瑞说你今天去检查了
Jerry said you had a check-up today...
有什么进展吗
Anything come up?
说来有趣
It's a funny thing.
-怎么了  -托米说我被安排动手术了
- What? - Tomi said I was scheduled for surgery.
他们把我排到了前面
They bumped me up in the line.
真好
That's good.
太好了  太好了
That's great. That's great.
-是吧  -等等
- Right? - Wait.
你是不是...
Did you...?
你做了什么
What did you do?
我没有...
I didn't...
我的债务被抹去了
My debt was wiped out.
霍恩斯比欠我一个人情
Hornsby owed me a favor.
这是作弊
It's cheating!
你为什么要这样做
Why would you do that?
因为我不想让你死
Because I don't want you to die.
卡萝尔
Carol.
排队都是骗人的
Those lines are a lie.
你觉得帕梅拉·弥尔顿
You think Pamela Milton would think twice
为她那混账儿子做这种事会迟疑吗
before doing the same thing for her shitty son?
你进过医院吗  卡萝尔
Have you been inside that hospital, Carol?
如果你进过  你就会看到那些人
'Cause if you had been, you'd see all those people,
受着苦
suffering,
和我一样
same as me.
等着接受治疗
Waiting for treatment.
和我一样
Same as me.
因为制度有问题  你就应该死吗
You're supposed to just die because the system is broken?
差劲的人心安理得地得到了更多
Lesser men have been given more and done nothing with it.
你不是差劲的人
You are not a lesser man.
我觉得那叫独裁
I think that's called an autocracy.
并不是
No, it's not.
自由并没有消失
Liberties haven't gone anywhere.
你是山顶寨的领袖
You're the leader at Hilltop.
你负责做决定
You make the decisions.
你认为你是独裁者吗
You consider yourself an autocrat?
我按照迪安娜和乔吉教我的方式领导社区
I-I lead the way I was taught by Deanna and Georgie.
我们建立的社区很公平
The communities that we built are fair.
联邦也很公平
The Commonwealth is fair.
但你比其他人
Yeah, but you drive a nicer car
开更好的车  住更好的房子
and live in a nicer house than everybody else.
我比普通工人的责任更大
I have more responsibilities than the average worker.
领袖必须让人们向往
A leader has to give her people something to look up to.
好吧  我希望人们向往我做成的事
Alright, well, I want people to look up to what I've done
我在做的事  而不是我的特权
and what I do, not what I have that they don't.
你身后
Behind you.
你来  还是我来
You want it or shall I?
我想对付你身后那个
Well, I was thinking about going after the one behind you.
乖
Hey, come on, now.
你还好吧
You okay?
很好  你呢
I'm great. How are you?
-你真会摆扑克脸  -谢谢
- You got a great poker face. - Thank you.
新工作如何
How's the new job going?
你知道的
Oh, you know.
很辛苦
It's a lot.
你后悔来这里吗
Do you regret coming here?
你后悔吗
Do you?
所以你喜欢这里
So you like it here?
我们可以聚在一起
We all get to be together.
大家都很安全  所以目前来说还好
Everyone's safe. So it works for now.
顺其自然
Going with the flow.
没想到我会成为一个警察
Didn't think I'd end up basically a cop,
但我做得挺好的  所以...
but I'm pretty good at it, so...
你做什么都很优秀  罗西塔
Pretty damn good at everything you do, Rosita.
谢谢  尤金
Thanks, Eugene.
但我确实很想家
I do miss home, though.
是啊
Yeah.
我想念去墙外  我想念过去的自由
I miss going outside the walls. I miss the freedom that we used to have.
但都会有的
But it'll come.
等亚历山大修好了
When Alexandria's fixed back up,
人们就会有选择  这是好事  知道吗
then -- then people have choices and that's good, you know?
你对未来很期待
You're excited about the future.
嗯  我猜是的
Yeah, I guess I am.
尤金  怎么了  说吧
Eugene, what is it? Spill.
我在想我们刚认识时
I was thinking about when we first met
我骗了你
and how I was lying to you.
关于我的身份  华盛顿  还有...
About who I was. About Washington, D.C. And...
那是很久以前的事了  尤金
That was a long time ago, Eugene.
我们找到了家  所以顺其自然是对的
And we found our home. So going with the flow works, right?
尤金  到底怎么回事
Eugene, what is it?
说吧  你会好受些的
Get it out. You'll feel better.
史蒂芬妮
Stephanie...
没有失踪
isn't missing.
我看到她了
I saw her.
她只是
She just...
和我分手了  她和我分手了
broke up with me. She broke up with me.
尤金  我很遗憾
Eugene, I'm so sorry.
她不是我认为的那个人
She wasn't who I thought she was.
去她的
Screw her.
你能找到更好的
You can do so much better.
你会找到对的那个人
And you're gonna find your person.
她就在某处  我保证
She's out there. I promise.
他们说的都是真的
They meant everything they said.
跟我们一起回来的士兵
All the Troopers that came back with us,
正在加固水塔
they're working on re-enforcing the water tower right now.
你和他们去打猎了吗
You went hunting with them?
对  收获不多  但是
Yeah. It's not much, but it's --
比过去几周好多了
More than we've had in weeks.
我们去做晚饭
Yeah, we'll get dinner started.
好  谢了
Alright. Thanks.
大家都好吗
Is everyone okay?
嗯  大家看起来松了一口气
Yeah, yeah. Everyone seems relieved.
希望这意味着我们今晚终于能睡觉了
Hoping this means we can actually get some sleep tonight.
达里尔
Daryl.
我还在想你什么时候回来
Was wondering when you'd come back.
你还好吗
How you holding up?
还好
Uh, it's okay.
-我们在尽力而为  -是吗
- We're doing our best. - Yeah?
只是感觉有些东西也许永远修不好了
Just feel like maybe some things just can't be fixed, you know?
有时感觉这一切都是徒劳
Just feels kind of pointless sometimes.
-我懂  -你怎么知道什么时候
- I hear you. - How do you know when?
什么意思
When what?
什么时候该离开
Just when it's time to walk away?
你想要这样做吗
Is that what you wanna do?
玛姬  我们分发一些补给可以吗
Hey, Maggie, is it okay if we hand out some supplies?
我们有足够多
We have more than enough.
食物  燃料
Food, fuel.
好  谢谢
Sure. Thank you.
很好  这就办
Great. We're on it.
你俩  跟我来
Uh, you two. Come with me.
达里尔  看我戴着什么
Hey, Daryl, look what I got.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我们要发食物了
Hey, we're gonna pass out some food.
-你想帮忙吗  -好
- You wanna help us? - Yeah.
大的给你
You take the big one.
送给伊莱哲
Hey, give this to Elijah.
好
Okay.
孩子在外面一定很难
Must be hard to be a kid out here.
他是在旅途中长大的
He grew up on the road.
他是另一种孩子
He's a different kind of kid.
你那朋友  她喜欢在外面折磨自己吗
Your friend. She like torturing herself out here?
这地方以前很特别
This place used to be really special.
与众不同
Different.
它现在陷入了困境  但是
It's going through hard times now, but
很快会恢复正常的
it'll be back up and running.
等着瞧吧
Just watch.
我猜不是所有地方都像亚历山大一样幸运
I guess not all places are as lucky as Alexandria.
不是所有地方都像联邦一样幸运
Not all places are as lucky as Commonwealth.
你改变心意了吗
Are you coming around?
还没到那一步
I wouldn't go that far,
但你们为我们做了不少好事  所以
but you guys, uh, have done good stuff for us, so,
这点我要承认
I don't know, I'll give you that.
联邦并不完美  哥们
Commonwealth ain't perfect, bro.
是吗
What, you think?
别太松懈了
Just don't get too comfortable.
你没穿盔甲只是因为
The only reason you're out of your armor
有人认为这样适合作秀
is because someone thought it'd be good for appearances.
你有你的角色  我也有我的角色
You got your role to play, and I got mine.
你醒来时我们会在这里
We'll be in here when you wake up.
披萨  冰淇淋  应有尽有
Pizza, ice cream. The works.
不
No.
不要菠萝
No pineapple.
我是认真的  杰瑞
I'm serious, Jerry.
披萨上放菠萝太荒唐了
Pineapple on pizza makes no sense.
披萨
Pizza?
你这段时间只能吃流食了
You're not eating anything but Jell-O for a while, hotshot.
紧张到手抖吗
Nervous twitch?
幸运币
Lucky coin.
我以前有一只幸运兔脚
I had a lucky rabbit's foot once.
我的狗连着兔子一起叼回来的
My dog brought it home with the rabbit still attached to it.
这是我父亲给我的
My old man gave this to me.
我小时候以为这是纯金的
When I was a kid, I thought it was made of gold.
结果只是镀金的
Turns out, it's just gold-plated.
里面不过是镍
Inside's same as a lowly nickel.
你决定了吗
Have you decided yet?
你能从中得到什么好处
What do you get out of all this?
得了吧  玛姬
Come on, Maggie.
别假装看不到眼前的现实
Let's not pretend the obvious isn't staring us in the face.
你力不从心
You're in over your head.
你不是很了解我
You don't know me very well.
我知道你很聪明  听得出什么是好提议
I know you're smart enough to know a good offer when you hear it.
而我也很聪明  知道我刚惹怒了你
And I'm smart enough to know I've just pissed you off.
你还没有回答我的问题
You haven't answered my question.
好吧  我说
Alright. I'll bite.
第一次去亚历山大时  我能看出来
The first time I went to Alexandria, I could see it.
巨大的潜力
The potential.
玛姬  你真的认为现在的山顶寨
Maggie, do you really believe that Hilltop, as it currently stands,
是你能拥有的最好的东西吗
is the best you'll ever have?
或者是亚历山大
Or Alexandria?
甚至是海边旅馆
Or even Oceanside?
看看周围
Look around.
我们能拥有更多
We can have so much more.
想象一下
Imagine
从联邦的音乐会接赫谢尔回家
being able to pick Hershel up from a concert at the Commonwealth,
带他去亚历山大看医生
take him to a doctor's appointment in Alexandria,
在海边旅馆乘船
then jump on a boat at Oceanside,
沿着海岸航行
traveling up the coast.
海岸上会有什么呢
And what's up that coast?
另一个港口城市
Another port town?
另一所学校
Another school?
一所大学怎么样
How about a university?
你有没有想象过送儿子去大学上大一
Have you ever imagined being able to drop your son off for his freshman year of college?
我曾试图建过
Tried to build it.
那当然了
Of course you did.
因为我们的看法一致
Because you and I see things the same way.
想象一下你想建立的那个世界
Imagine the world you want to build.
记住这个想法
Hold it in your mind.
现在想象一下五万个联邦工人
Now picture the power of 50,000 Commonwealth workers
帮你实现这个设想
helping you make that vision a reality.
想想到了那时  你能做到什么
Think what you could accomplish then.
尸群来了
Swarm incoming!
这边
This way.
开火
Fire!
想象一下每次警报响起
Imagine not having to deal with this
都不用应付行尸
every time that alarm goes off.
对啊  我们可以一直建设
Yeah, we could keep building.
不用再建建停停了
No more starts and stops.
我知道有很多要考虑的
I know there's a lot to consider,
但看看周围
but, I mean, look around.
我们需要这个
We need this.
我知道
I know.
列队
Formation!
快点
Let's go!
迪克森  入列
Dixon. Fall in.
稍等
Hold up.
记住  他们一直在看着
Remember, they're always watching.
懂吗
Got me?
嗯  我懂
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
向左转
Left face.
齐步走
Forward march.
这里从不无聊  是吧
Never a dull moment here, is there?
我们尽力了
We try.
大家还好吗
Everyone okay?
嗯  没人受伤  四肢完好
Yeah, no injuries, all limbs intact.
我觉得这算个好日子
I'd call that a good day.
但山顶寨不会接受你的提议
But the Hilltop's gonna pass on your offer.
我能问原因吗
Can I ask why?
因为就像你说的  一切都有代价
'Cause, like you said, everything costs something.
不  请别关门
No, please don't shut the door.
我在类似内幕冰淇淋的店里找到了美味树莓
Found some raspberry goodness of the Inside Scoop variety.
这不是黑树莓  但是
It's not exactly black raspberry, but...
拜托了  很冰的
please, it's very cold.
我很抱歉  麦克斯
Um, I'm so sorry, Max.
因为我不绅士的行为
For my ungentleman-like behavior.
逃避和不听你说话
For running away. For not listening.
我当时伤心而困惑
I was bruised and confused.
-你当时很无礼  -是的
- You were pretty damn rude. - I was.
的确
Indeed.
我让霍恩斯比操控了我
I let Hornsby get inside my head,
那是一场史无前例的心理入侵
and it was an infiltration of the most epic proportions.
他是条毒蛇
He is a snake.
更像条虫子
More like a worm.
我让一个冒牌货进入了我的心房
I let an imposter into my heart
还有我的家
and my home.
-我让她读了我的手稿  -手稿
- I let her read my manuscript. - Manuscript?
我
I --
我在写一本小说
I'm writing a novel.
里面有墓室吗
Was a sepulcher involved?
显然有
Obviously.
是不是发生在喀尔巴阡山
Did it take place in the Carpathian Mountains?
喀尔巴阡山  对
Carpathian Mountains, yes.
你竟然让她读了
You let her read it?
我以为她是你
I thought she was you.
我知道  但是  尤金
I know, but, Eugene...
怎会这样
how?
我们在一起那么久
After all that time we spent together,
告诉了彼此那么多
everything we told each other,
你怎会不知道她不是我
how could you not know it wasn't me?
我不知道
I do-- I don't know.
我猜很早以前  我就发现了
I guess I figured out a long time ago
我和大部分人不一样
that I'm not like most folks.
我很早就习惯了被拒绝
I got used to rejection PDQ.
有时我甚至都没意识到那是拒绝
Didn't even realize it was rejection some of the times,
但可以说  这种事经常发生
but, well, suffice it to say, it happened a fair amount.
所以我总是怀疑我们的感情只是幻觉
So there was a part of me that always wondered if our connection was all in my head.
但在我来了这里后  她没有
But when I got here, and she didn't...
将我推开
push me away...
我迫切希望这份感情是真的
I just so badly wanted this to be real.
以至于有时忽略了微小的线索
And subtle cues escape me sometimes.
总之  我从没想过要伤害你  麦克斯
Anyway, I never meant to hurt you, Max.
但我的意图不能成为后果的借口
But my intent does not excuse my impact.
我如何才能补偿你  你允许我试试吗
How can I make this up to you? Will you allow me to try?
我不知道
I don't know.
我能读你的小说吗
Can I read your novel?
说来不幸
Well, as ill fortune would have it,
你来见我时  我正在烧唯一的实体版
you came upon me whilst I was burning the only physical copy.
不过  大部分内容我已经记住了
However, I have committed much of the text to memory.
概念是什么
What was the concept?
一个叫史蒂芬·波特曼的侦探
A gumshoe by the name of Steph Portman
被卷入了轰轰烈烈的国际劫案中
is caught up in a rollicking international caper,
他试图避免核灾难
trying to avert nuclear disaster
并应对国内错综复杂的法律官僚体系
and navigate the intricacies of the legal bureaucracies back at home.
你没把地方检察官写成贪官吧
You didn't make the District Attorney corrupt, did you?
当然没有
Certainly not.
那种老套没人会惊喜
That would've surprised exactly no one.
但我给他了一个恶毒的孪生兄弟
I did, however, give him an unsavory twin brother.
邪恶的孪生兄弟  不错
Evil twin. Nice.
我也这样觉得
Yeah, I thought so.
你应该把那个孪生兄弟写成科学家
You should, um, make the twin a scientist.
加大核威胁的风险
Ramp up the stakes on the nuclear threat.
我正是这样写的
That is exactly what I did.
怎么了
What?
感觉就像过去
Just...felt like old times.
我有样东西要给你
Here. I got something for ya.
朱迪思给的
It's from Judith.
她说以防你再逼赫谢尔吃马肉
She said in case you're making Hershel eat more horse meat.
天啊
Oh, God.
很高兴见到你
It was good to see you.
嗯
Yeah.
保重
Be careful.
如果你需要我  你知道去哪找我
If you need me, you know where to find me.
你也是
Same for you.
戴安
Dianne?
我要走了  玛姬
I'm leaving, Maggie.
有些人要跟我一起去
Some of the others are coming with me,
你也应该去
and you should, too.
你得小心该信任谁
You need to be careful who you trust.
你比任何人都懂这点
You know that better than anybody.
你也得知道何时该求助
You also have to know when to ask for help.
现在比以往更困难  不必如此的
It's harder than it has ever been, and it doesn't have to be.
我非常敬重你
I respect the hell outta you,
但我撑不住了
but I can't do this anymore.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这是一次值得肯定的努力  兰斯
It was a worthy effort, Lance.
还没结束
It's not over.
不必结束
It doesn't have to be.
该回家了
It's time to go home.
我们还有亚历山大
We still have Alexandria.
我只是需要时间说服剩下两个社区
I just need time to get the other two.
一次试图纳入三个新社区很大胆
It was a bold move, trying to bring three new communities into the fold.
我理解这种事为何会吸引你
I get why something like that would be appealing to you.
毕竟得有人管它们  对吧
Someone needs to run them, right?
那个人选将由你决定
That selection would be at your discretion,
显而易见
obviously.
Obviously.
我会假装你做这事
I'm gonna pretend that you were doing this
是为了联邦  而不是为了你自己
for the good of the Commonwealth rather than for yourself.
我这是为了你
I was doing this for you.
自我们认识以来  你一直野心勃勃  兰斯
You've been ambitious our whole lives, Lance.
野心向来难以收敛  所以
Ambition is notoriously hard to reel in. So...
你想试着做成这事  当然可以
if you want to try and make it work, fine.
但如果你懈怠了家里的工作
But if your job at home starts to suffer,
将会有后果的
there will be consequences.
联邦永远摆在第一位
The Commonwealth always comes first.
兰斯
Lance.
兰斯  你还好吗
Lance, you okay?
好极了
"A" Plus.
她是怎么说亚历山大的
What'd she say about Alexandria?
一切还好吗
We good?
一切都好
Everything's fine.
帕梅拉同意了
Pamela's on board.
实际上  我们会带来更多人
In fact, we're gonna bring even more people in.
做好准备  亚伦
Get ready, Aaron.
我们将重塑这个世界
We are going to remake the world.